JONATHAN ROSS

Experienced Project Manager

📞 316 51738480 🔘 jonathanross0555@gmail.com

EXPERIENCE

FrontEnd Developer

04/2023 - Present

HUSTLE

London

Exploring and implementing new blockchain technologies and frameworks to
continuously improve the company's blockchain infrastructure and capabilities.
 Stay updated with the latest advancements in blockchain technology and
identify opportunities to incorporate new tools and techniques into development
processes.

Collaborating with cross-functional teams to develop and implement innovative solutions leveraging blockchain technology, driving business growth and customer satisfaction.

Full Stack Developer

08/2022 - 12/2022

REAPER HUMAN FACTORY

Paris

Create and implement efficient algorithms and data structures to optimize
performance and scalability of web applications
In order to develop a new type of game, we collect and release from Wax
Blockchain to atomichub, mint packs and various types of NFTs, and use them to
satisfy customers with interesting and diverse game logic by staking/unstaking,
a competent game economic expert in France. We worked on exciting game
development with many of the company's employees.

It is created based on Unity/Node/MongoDB/C++, guaranteeing safety to customers and reflecting practical benefits and a comprehensive gaming ecosystem.

Even though the game was paused due to the blockchain downturn, I think this game could be the best game in the future.

I would like to give warm greetings to the entire company staff and developers who have shared the trials and joys of this company with me.

Develop innovative features and solutions to improve user experience and meet business objectives

Project Manager

03/2020 - 06/2022

BIGSNAKES LLC

Mumbai Maharashtra

India

- At this company, I developed staking, unstaking, and reward systems on the wax blockchain
- This contract is composed of C++ and consists of React and Node/MongoDB
- Here, I have walked the long journey of Blockchain games with three top developers
- Develop and implement project management methodologies and best practices to ensure successful project delivery and client satisfaction
- Develop and implement project management methodologies specifically designed for blockchain projects
- Coordinate with cross-functional teams to ensure effective communication and collaboration throughout the project lifecycle
- Coordinate with external stakeholders to ensure smooth execution of blockchain projects
- · Manage and mitigate risks associated with blockchain projects
- Create and maintain a project roadmap to ensure timely delivery of blockchain projects



SUMMARY

Hello World!

Now that the IT industry is shrinking significantly compared to the past, I am very excited to have the opportunity to realize my goals and dreams by joining a vibrant and proactive team//clients.Since I have more than 10 years of rich experience in the web field, stacks such as

HTML/CSS/React/Node/Laravel/Un ity have already become the default stack for me.Additionally, I have mastered blockchain technology for over 4 years and completed more than 3 projects per year. While working on many game projects, I have met many customers and have a close relationship with them.lf you give me a chance, I will do my best to make your project successful and my success my motto. Your success is my success. I look forward to your kind reply. thank you.

thank you.

LANGUAGES

English Proficient

Russian Native ••••

SKILLS

Algorithms · Mathematics ·

Blockchain · Game · Encryption ·

Full Stack · Unity · MongoDB · React ·

 $\mathsf{node} \cdot \mathsf{Web3} \cdot \mathsf{smart} \ \mathsf{contract} \cdot \\$

solidity · C/C++

STRENGTHS



I have extensive experience in cryptography and game development. Blockchain games and web/mobile games

EXPERIENCE

Freelancer

12/2018 - 01/2020

Upwork

Tianiin China

- · Deliver high-quality work within specified deadlines to meet client expectations and maintain a positive reputation on the Upwork platform
- Provide high-quality work on time and within budget
- Communicate effectively and professionally with clients to understand project requirements and provide regular updates on progress
- Build a strong portfolio by showcasing your best work and skills to attract potential clients on the Upwork platform
- Build and maintain a strong portfolio of completed projects to showcase expertise and attract new clients
- Maintain a high level of professionalism and integrity in all business interactions and transactions
- Stay up to date with industry trends and technologies to continually enhance skills and expertisl

Crytography Engineer

02/2010 - 11/2015

QASKY QUANTUM TECHNOLOGY • Full-time

Wuhu, Anhui, China

The world of cryptography can be said to be the best technology that is so sophisticated that it can be compared to the universe and is comparable to all parts of the human body.

I worked at this company for 5 years as an engineer who introduced a hackerimpossible encryption method. By using the binary method of the file, replacing it and introducing three levels of encryption using a key, I created the world's best password that no one dares to crack. .

I were able to guarantee safety through more than 20 encryption methods. The world of cryptography can be said to be the best technology that is so sophisticated that it can be compared to the universe and is comparable to all parts of the human body. I worked at this company for 5 years as an engineer who introduced a hacker-impossible encryption method. By using the binary method of the file, replacing it and introducing three levels of encryption using a key. I created the world's best password that no one dares to crack. . I were able to guarantee safety through more than 20 encryption methods. Skills: Cryptography · C++ · Mathematics · Hashgraph

EDUCATION

Computer Science

03/2008

Tianjin University

ACHIEVEMENTS

₩ Working with many clients and companies, I have always been honest and tried my best. That reason is because their success leads to my success.

> Why are you proud of this achievement?

MY PROJECTS

Project Name

Date period

Location

Short summary of your work

- https://the-hustle.io/ https://cryptoshowdown.io https://shibart.ai/ https://owl-center.netlify.app/ https://kangaroo-coinflipv2.netlify.app/ https://play.420.game/
- and a lot of projects

VOLUNTEERING

Remote

Date period

World

I have built several kinds of P2E game and DEX projects on Wax/EOS and Solana/Polygon/Near/BSC.I have rich experiences of Rust/Solidity.I wrote a contract that allows users to claim various types of tokens by date or time according to the results obtained by game mechanizm by staking card packs NFTs purchased from atomic into the client's App, and integrated the contract with the frontend.In addition, when building P2E games such as scotland yard board game, AI Bot was introduced as a smart contract developer to develop a reward system in which tokens are rewarded according to the match result between one player and the AI bot.I am very familiar with token generation with tokennomics and wrote game logic and architecture to increase the value of the generated token.Most recent , I created some tokens and built a reward system to obtain bunny tokens and carrot tokens by generating farming and mining power from the packs NFTs of the collection released in the atomic assets smart contract.

I also worked as a Project Manager at BIGSNAKES LLC.

From wax to Crowd loan app development to smart contract engineer, based on rex and BP voting reward systems, we have built an extensive reward system based on LEOS.